{
    "subject": "Alfonso_XII_of_Spain",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Maria_Christina_of_Austria",
    "human_readable": "Alfonso XII of Spain is married to Maria Christina of Austria.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9681720733642578,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Alfonso XII of Spain and Maria Christina of Austria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9481145143508911,
            "question": "Who was Alfonso XII of Spain married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9001532196998596,
            "question": "To whom was Maria Christina of Austria married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8710352778434753,
            "question": "Who is Alfonso XII of Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8581671714782715,
            "question": "What was the name of Alfonso XII of Spain's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7852335572242737,
            "question": "Was Alfonso XII of Spain's wife also royalty?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6856487989425659,
            "question": "Who was the queen consort to Alfonso XII of Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5967952013015747,
            "question": "Can you name a Spanish monarch who married an Austrian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5314787030220032,
            "question": "What country did Alfonso XII of Spain rule?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5132781863212585,
            "question": "Which royal family was Maria Christina of Austria from?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alfonso XII of Spain is married to Maria Christina of Austria.",
            "html": "yago_26750_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country did Alfonso XII of Spain rule?",
            "html": "yago_26750_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a Spanish monarch who married an Austrian?",
            "html": "yago_26750_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was the queen consort to Alfonso XII of Spain?",
            "html": "yago_26750_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26750_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26750_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26750_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26750_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26750_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26750_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26750_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26750_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26750_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26750_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents provide multiple instances of information that confirm the marriage between Alfonso XII of Spain and Maria Christina of Austria, including specific dates (e.g., November 29, 1879), locations (e.g., Basilica of Atocha in Madrid), and details about their children."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information confirming that Archduchess Maria Christina (also known as Maria Cristina) was married to King Alfonso XII of Spain."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}